<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Richard&#39;s Page</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Richard&#39;s Page</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>In Appreciation of debugonce()</title>
      <link>/post/2021/07/10/in-appreciation-of-debugonce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/07/10/in-appreciation-of-debugonce/</guid>
      <description>It’s not often I find a new base R functions but a coworker recently put me on to a function that I’ve been using a ton. Most of the R development work we do with the Reds involves developing inside of packages. That often means working with functions inside of functions inside of functions which can make debugging difficult when updating code.
debugonce() is a function that Hadley mentions in Advanced R Chapter 22 but that I had never seen and see very little mention of elsewhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Post at Open Source Football</title>
      <link>/post/2021/07/10/new-post-at-open-source-football/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/07/10/new-post-at-open-source-football/</guid>
      <description>I have a new post up at Open Source Football where I build some multilevel models in stan to estimate team ability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun With Spotify&#39;s API</title>
      <link>/post/2021/07/07/fun-with-spotify-s-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/07/07/fun-with-spotify-s-api/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been interested in getting better with purrr’s map functions and have always wanted to get my hands dirty with the Spotify API so this post has a little bit of both. We’ll use the wonderful spotifyr package to take a look at trends in which NFL players are hot topics of conversation on top Fantasy Football podcasts.
The first step was to identify a list of podcasts and pull their information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Measuring Run/Pass Tendencies with tidyModels and nflfastR</title>
      <link>/post/2020/09/08/measuring-run-pass-tendencies-with-tidymodels-and-nflfastr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/09/08/measuring-run-pass-tendencies-with-tidymodels-and-nflfastr/</guid>
      <description>Note: A slightly revised version of this post was posted at Open Source Football.
As a Seahawks fan who spends a good amount of time online I’ve been exposed to a lot of discussion about the value of running vs. passing. A point used in favor of a rushing-focused attack is that good teams tend to run the ball a lot. This is usually met with the response that teams who are ahead will run to kill clock and minimize risk, meaning the causal arrow is backwards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello! I am a data scientist who currently serves as the Assistant Director of Quantitative Analysis for the Los Angeles Angels. Prior to my time with the Angels I got a Ph.D. in Political Science from the University of Michigan and a B.A. in Political Science from the University of Washington.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>